module.exports = [
	{
		_id: '6001e313576807a20b7aa0b2',
		selection: ['Humpback Whale', 'Blue Whale', 'Elephant', 'Bluefin Whale'],
		question: 'What is biggest animal in the world?',
		answer: 'Blue Whale',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6001e4c1576807a20b7aa0b3',
		selection: ['A cub', 'A rabbit', 'A kit', 'A slag'],
		question: 'What is a baby rabbit called?',
		answer: 'A kit',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6001e57e576807a20b7aa0b4',
		selection: ['Human Psychology', 'Insects', 'Babies', 'Formation of rocks'],
		question: 'Entomology is the study of?',
		answer: 'Insects',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6001e5f6576807a20b7aa0b5',
		selection: [
			'Democratic Party',
			'Nuclear Party',
			'Nazi Party',
			'Colonoscopy'
		],
		question: 'Hitler party is known as',
		answer: 'Nazi Party',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6001ef9608f91da6ed3b0fb5',
		selection: ['Tree', 'Land', 'Ammonites', 'Water'],
		question: 'Sharks have existed before the first',
		answer: 'Tree',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60020e5aaac5bfabbc76f7d8',
		selection: [
			'Scrooge McDuck',
			'Tony Stark',
			'Bruce Wayne',
			'Martha Stewart'
		],
		question: 'Richest fictional character',
		answer: 'Scrooge McDuck',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60020eabaac5bfabbc76f7d9',
		selection: ['Tony Stark', 'Rihanna', 'Benedict Cumberbatch', 'Rob Vicious'],
		question: 'Voice of Smaug from The Hobbit',
		answer: 'Benedict Cumberbatch',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60021bb71297f1aea1d12926',
		selection: ['Arm', 'Torso', 'Leg', 'Butt'],
		question: 'Which part of the body would you find the fibula',
		answer: 'Leg',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60022bd9b2f263b18b97e095',
		selection: ['Vietnam', 'Indonesia', 'Philippines', 'India'],
		question: 'Which of these countries is not in South East Asia',
		answer: 'India',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60022c5ab2f263b18b97e096',
		selection: ['Alphabet', 'Facebook', 'BMW', 'Steve Jobs'],
		question: 'Parent company of Google',
		answer: 'Alphabet',
		completed: false,
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600257dfc55586b65fd0ba0f',
		selection: ['360', '10', '9', '-2'],
		question: 'How many days was Javascript built in',
		answer: '10',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025886a23240b67581f2bf',
		selection: [
			'Nicholas Cage',
			'Michael Scott',
			'Dwayne "The Sock" Johnson',
			'Adam Levine'
		],
		question: 'Lead singer of Maroon 5',
		answer: 'Adam Levine',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025975a23240b67581f2c1',
		selection: ['Drake', 'Eminem', 'Neil Degrasse Mike Tyson', 'Seti'],
		question:
			'_____ equation is used to determine the number of active alien civilizations in the Milky Way',
		answer: 'Drake',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025a1fa23240b67581f2c2',
		selection: ['400m/s', '250m/s', '343m/s', 'Speed of light + 1 m/s'],
		question: 'Speed of sound at 20Â°C is',
		answer: '343m/s',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025a79a23240b67581f2c3',
		selection: ['Catering Service', 'Hotel', 'Investor', 'Serial Killer'],
		question: 'Warren Buffett is a famous',
		answer: 'Investor',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025b88afeea3b710d62aeb',
		selection: ['The 6 step', 'The 2 Timer', 'Windmill', 'Das Flip'],
		question: 'One of these is a breakdance powermove',
		answer: 'Windmill',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025c97afeea3b710d62aec',
		selection: ['Neil Armstrong', 'Ted Mosby', 'Mr Bean', 'Lance Armstrong'],
		question: 'First man on the moon',
		answer: 'Neil Armstrong',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025d2fafeea3b710d62aed',
		selection: [
			'Lee Harvey Oswald',
			'Darth Vader',
			'John Wilkes Booth',
			'Ted Mosby'
		],
		question: 'JFK was assassinated by ',
		answer: 'Lee Harvey Oswald',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025d6eafeea3b710d62aee',
		selection: [
			'Darth Obiwan',
			'James Franco',
			'Darth Vader',
			'Morgan Freeman'
		],
		question: 'Luke and Leia were the children of ',
		answer: 'Darth Vader',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025decb9d9e8b7a6f0f320',
		selection: [
			'Yolo Swaggins',
			'Gandalf the Geese',
			'Samwise Gamgee',
			'Frodo Baggins'
		],
		question: 'Who was the ringbearer in the Fellowship of the Ring',
		answer: 'Frodo Baggins',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025ec64dc1c6b7cf34f3da',
		selection: ['Sloths', 'Fish', 'Humans', 'Manatees'],
		question: 'Giraffes have same number of bones in their necks as',
		answer: 'Humans',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025f084dc1c6b7cf34f3db',
		selection: ['Pluto', 'Mercury', 'Uranus', 'Venus'],
		question: 'Closest planet to the sun',
		answer: 'Mercury',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025fa84dc1c6b7cf34f3dc',
		selection: ['United States', 'Russia', 'Australia', 'Canada'],
		question: 'Country with the largest land mass',
		answer: 'Russia',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60025fd84dc1c6b7cf34f3dd',
		selection: ['Moo', 'Meow', 'Woof', 'CAW CAW'],
		question: 'Sound that cats make',
		answer: 'Meow',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600260534dc1c6b7cf34f3de',
		selection: ['Charles Xavier', 'Dan', 'Saitama', 'Chad'],
		question: "One Punch Man's real name",
		answer: 'Saitama',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600263024dc1c6b7cf34f3e0',
		selection: [
			'Uncle Found Out',
			'Unified Field Observation',
			'Unidentified Flying Object',
			'I Owe Yous'
		],
		question: 'U.F.O stands for',
		answer: 'Unidentified Flying Object',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002d987d32b82c1bb12b791',
		selection: ['Stiglets', 'Sticklers', 'Aglets', 'Mippets'],
		question: 'End of a shoelace is called ',
		answer: 'Aglets',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002da5699cad0c21578f315',
		selection: ['Skull', 'Pelvis', 'Chest', 'Mouth'],
		question: 'The human brain lives in the ',
		answer: 'Skull',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002e9cf0782d9c7227756aa',
		selection: [
			'TAKE ME BY THE HAND',
			'MADE ME A MAN',
			'THAT ONE NIGHT',
			'Dinner Party'
		],
		question: 'Best The Office episode',
		answer: 'Dinner Party',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002f86420b4c3ca83f7dd0b',
		selection: ['K', 'Ts', 'P', 'Po'],
		question: 'Chemical symbol for Potassium',
		answer: 'K',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002f87f20b4c3ca83f7dd0c',
		selection: ['China', 'Siam', 'Ankor Wat', 'Burma'],
		question: 'Official name of Thailand before 1939',
		answer: 'Siam',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002f89f20b4c3ca83f7dd0d',
		selection: ['Yemen', 'Vatican City', 'Monaco', 'San Marino'],
		question: "World's smallest country",
		answer: 'Vatican City',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002f8c420b4c3ca83f7dd0e',
		selection: [
			'Smooth criminal',
			'Remember the time',
			'Earth song',
			'I just had sex'
		],
		question: 'Which of these is NOT a Michael Jackson song',
		answer: 'I just had sex',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002f8e820b4c3ca83f7dd0f',
		selection: ['Echolocation', 'X-ray vision', 'Sixth sense', 'Talking'],
		question: 'How are bats able to fly in the dark',
		answer: 'Echolocation',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002f8fd20b4c3ca83f7dd10',
		selection: ['1942', '1945', '1948', '2012'],
		question: 'What year did World War II end',
		answer: '1945',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002f92620b4c3ca83f7dd11',
		selection: [
			'Musical instrument',
			'Heart rate monitor',
			'Stereo telephone',
			'Tool measuring waves'
		],
		question: 'What is a xylophone',
		answer: 'Musical instrument',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002f95920b4c3ca83f7dd13',
		selection: ['Yuan', 'Yen', 'Yang', 'Sushi'],
		question: 'Name the currency used in Japan',
		answer: 'Yen',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002fa0520b4c3ca83f7dd14',
		selection: ['Air Trafficker', 'Plumber', 'Dentist', 'Civil Engineer'],
		question: 'Electric chair was invented by a ',
		answer: 'Dentist',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6002fa5420b4c3ca83f7dd15',
		selection: ['Honey', 'Corns', 'Rice', 'Cherries'],
		question: "Only food that doesn't spoil",
		answer: 'Honey',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600357355fb36ed1bddef16c',
		selection: ['aaahhh', 'Bruce Willis', "Baby don't hurt me", "I don't care"],
		question: 'What is love?',
		answer: "Baby don't hurt me",
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60036be1f134d0d6da4cadb8',
		selection: ['1802', '1776', '2020', '1492'],
		question: 'Year the declaration of independence pronouncement',
		answer: '1776',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004bdb6d41f8b0015496c9d',
		selection: ['China', 'Russia', 'United States', 'India'],
		question: 'Country with highest population',
		answer: 'China',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004be29d41f8b0015496c9e',
		selection: ['Protoplasm', 'Cytoplasm', 'Organelles', 'Who cares?'],
		question: 'Physical phase of life is called',
		answer: 'Protoplasm',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004be69d41f8b0015496c9f',
		selection: ['-40', '0', '-20', '16'],
		question:
			' At what temperature are Farenheit and Celsius equal to each other?',
		answer: '-40',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004be86d41f8b0015496ca0',
		selection: ['Mercury', 'Jupiter', 'Saturn', 'Earth'],
		question: 'Which planet has the most moons',
		answer: 'Jupiter',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004becfd41f8b0015496ca1',
		selection: ['Insulator', 'Conductor', 'SemiConductor', 'Metal'],
		question: 'What material does not carry an electrical charge',
		answer: 'Insulator',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004beebd41f8b0015496ca2',
		selection: ['Vitamin C', 'Vitamin D', 'Vitamin F', 'Vitamin 9'],
		question: 'How to cure scurvy',
		answer: 'Vitamin C',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004bf2cd41f8b0015496ca3',
		selection: [
			'Glucose',
			'Fructose',
			'Sucrose',
			"The brain doesn't need energy"
		],
		question: 'What kind of sugar does the brain need for energy',
		answer: 'Glucose',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004bfdad41f8b0015496ca4',
		selection: [
			'Universal Serial Bus',
			'Universal System Bus',
			'Universal Selector Bus',
			'U Suck B***s'
		],
		question: 'What does USB stand for',
		answer: 'Universal Serial Bus',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004bff6d41f8b0015496ca5',
		selection: ['Time', 'Waves', 'Wind', 'Sound'],
		question: 'What does a chronometer measure',
		answer: 'Time',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c027d41f8b0015496ca6',
		selection: ['Carbon Dioxide', 'Oxygen', 'Nitrogen', 'Uranium'],
		question: 'Which frozen gas forms dry ice',
		answer: 'Carbon Dioxide',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c04ed41f8b0015496ca7',
		selection: ['Hair', 'Nerves', 'Skin', 'Blood'],
		question: 'Alopecia is the loss of ',
		answer: 'Hair',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c0e0d41f8b0015496ca8',
		selection: ['Drive', 'Cook', 'Run', 'Do Math'],
		question: 'Albert Einstein never learned to',
		answer: 'Drive',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c114d41f8b0015496ca9',
		selection: ['70%', '80%', '90%', '100%'],
		question: 'About what percentage of the world is water',
		answer: '70%',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c130d41f8b0015496caa',
		selection: [
			'Bacterial infection',
			'Viral infection',
			'Whenever you want',
			'Never'
		],
		question: 'When should you take antibiotics',
		answer: 'Bacterial infection',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c158d41f8b0015496cab',
		selection: ['200', '100', '300', '400'],
		question: 'About how many countries are in the world',
		answer: '200',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c182d41f8b0015496cac',
		selection: ['American', 'Pacific', 'Indian', 'Arctic'],
		question: 'Which of these is not a major ocean',
		answer: 'American',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c1a0d41f8b0015496cad',
		selection: ['8', '9', '10', '7'],
		question: 'How many planets are in the solar system',
		answer: '8',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c1c7d41f8b0015496cae',
		selection: ['Islam', 'Hinduism', 'Buddhuism', 'Judaism'],
		question: 'The Quran is the holy book of which religion',
		answer: 'Islam',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c1fbd41f8b0015496caf',
		selection: ['Multiple Gods', 'One God', 'Angels', 'Martyrs'],
		question: 'If a religion is polytheistic, it has ',
		answer: 'Multiple Gods',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c223d41f8b0015496cb0',
		selection: [
			'Genetic factors',
			'Vaccines',
			'Influenza',
			'Eating spicy food'
		],
		question: 'Which of these things cause autism?',
		answer: 'Genetic factors',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c253d41f8b0015496cb1',
		selection: ['Earthquakes', 'Droughts', 'Tornados', 'Volcanoes'],
		question: 'What is the Pacific Ring of Fire known for',
		answer: 'Earthquakes',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c283d41f8b0015496cb2',
		selection: ['India', 'Japan', 'Siberia', 'Syria'],
		question: 'Which country does yoga come from',
		answer: 'India',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c2abd41f8b0015496cb3',
		selection: ['Denmark', 'Norway', 'Sweden', 'The Netherlandsss'],
		question: 'Which of these countries is not part of Scandinavia',
		answer: 'The Netherlands',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c2d0d41f8b0015496cb4',
		selection: ['Qatar', 'Italy', 'Wakanda', 'Vietnam'],
		question: 'Which country is shaped like a boot',
		answer: 'Italy',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c307d41f8b0015496cb5',
		selection: ['1%', '2%', '33%', '4%'],
		question: "What percentage of the world's population has red hair",
		answer: '2%',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004c661d41f8b0015496cb6',
		selection: [
			'Detective',
			'Having dead parents',
			'Super strength',
			'Eye beams'
		],
		question: 'Batman\'s "superpower" is ',
		answer: 'Detective',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6004e3449374760015228490',
		selection: [
			'George Washington',
			'Bill Gates',
			'John Adams',
			'Thomas Jefferson'
		],
		question: 'First president of the United States',
		answer: 'George Washington',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60050221e92dc30015769c53',
		selection: ['Almonds', 'Peanuts', 'Cashews', 'Acorns'],
		question: 'What nut is used to make marzipan',
		answer: 'Almonds',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60050289e92dc30015769c54',
		selection: ['3', '2', '4', 'No government'],
		question: 'How many branches make up the US government',
		answer: '3',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600502ffe92dc30015769c56',
		selection: ['Butt', 'Triceps', 'Thighs', 'Tongue'],
		question: 'What is the largest muscle in the human body',
		answer: 'Butt',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60050387e92dc30015769c57',
		selection: ['Octopus', 'Sharks', 'Manatees', 'Rock Fish'],
		question: 'Which sea creature has 3 hearts?',
		answer: 'Octopus',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600503c0e92dc30015769c58',
		selection: [
			'Helen of Troy',
			'Barbara of Wilkeshire',
			'Katy Perry',
			'Martha Stewart'
		],
		question: 'Whose face was said to have launched 1,000 ships?',
		answer: 'Helen of Troy',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600503d4e92dc30015769c59',
		selection: ['3', '2', '4', '12'],
		question: 'how many pedals do most modern pianos have?',
		answer: '3',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60050422e92dc30015769c5a',
		selection: ['Indian', 'African', 'Southern', 'Arctic'],
		question: 'Which ocean surrounds the Maldives?',
		answer: 'Indian',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6005046ae92dc30015769c5b',
		selection: ['Chernobyl', 'Chimaobi', 'London', 'Nuketown'],
		question: 'Russian town that suffered a nuclear disaster in 1986',
		answer: 'Chernobyl',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600504cce92dc30015769c5c',
		selection: ['Shanghai', 'Beijing', 'Maktu', 'Pinguo'],
		question: 'What is the capital of China',
		answer: 'Beijing',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600504fce92dc30015769c5d',
		selection: ['7', '6', '4', '9'],
		question: 'Number of colors in a rainbow',
		answer: '7',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60050536e92dc30015769c5e',
		selection: ['26', '24', '28', '30'],
		question: 'How many letters in the English alphabet',
		answer: '26',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60050590e92dc30015769c5f',
		selection: ['Nose and Ears', 'Nose and Eyes', 'Hands and Feet', 'Neck'],
		question: 'Which two body parts never stop growing',
		answer: 'Nose and Ears',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600505c4e92dc30015769c60',
		selection: ['1914', '1912', '1910', '1942'],
		question: 'What year did World War 1 begin',
		answer: '1914',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60050622e92dc30015769c61',
		selection: ['Inner core', 'Outer core', 'Crust', 'Mantle'],
		question: 'Which layer of Earth is made up of tectonic plates',
		answer: 'Crust',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6005064be92dc30015769c62',
		selection: ['A sword', 'A frog', 'A car', 'A shape'],
		question: 'What is a rapier',
		answer: 'A sword',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6005068ee92dc30015769c63',
		selection: ['52', '49', '12', '68'],
		question: 'How many cards in a complete pack of cards',
		answer: '52',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600506aee92dc30015769c64',
		selection: ['Africa', 'North America', 'Asia', 'Pandora'],
		question: 'Hottest continent on Earth',
		answer: 'Africa',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60050714e92dc30015769c65',
		selection: ['90%', '99%', '50%', '25%'],
		question: 'What percentage of marine life lives in the photic zone',
		answer: '90%',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60062091c3ddbb0015b18622',
		selection: ['24 hours', '12 hours', '6 days', 'Immortal'],
		question: 'Lifespan of a dragon fly',
		answer: '24 hours',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600620f3c3ddbb0015b18623',
		selection: ['1912', '1970', '1896', '2001'],
		question: 'What year did the Titanic sink',
		answer: '1912',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60062144c3ddbb0015b18624',
		selection: ['Tom Hanks', 'Tim Honks', 'Bill Gates', 'Ted Mosby'],
		question: 'Which actor played Forrest Gump',
		answer: 'Tom Hanks',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600621bbc3ddbb0015b18625',
		selection: ['99%', '91%', '95%', '87%'],
		question: 'About how much % is the mass of the solar system the sun',
		answer: '99%',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60062230c3ddbb0015b18627',
		selection: ['Italy', 'China', 'Russia', 'England'],
		question: 'Where is the colosseum located',
		answer: 'Italy',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60062245c3ddbb0015b18628',
		selection: ['Cambodia', 'Thailand', 'Laos', 'Vietnam'],
		question: 'Where is Angkor Wat located',
		answer: 'Cambodia',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60062422c3ddbb0015b18629',
		selection: ['Mjolnir', 'Vanir', 'Aesir', 'Valekov'],
		question: "What is the name of Thor's hammer",
		answer: 'Mjolnir',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '6006255fc3ddbb0015b1862a',
		selection: [
			'Fights germs in the blood',
			'Deoxygenates blood',
			'Moderates temperature',
			'Absorbs nutrients'
		],
		question: 'What is one function of the spleen',
		answer: 'Fights germs in the blood',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '60062595c3ddbb0015b1862b',
		selection: ['Alveoli', 'Lipids', 'Vitols', 'Jeff'],
		question: 'What are the air sacs in the lungs called',
		answer: 'Alveoli',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600dd1ae71128e7eb0127822',
		selection: ['California', 'Colorado', 'Maine', 'New York'],
		question: 'First state to legalize medical cannabis',
		answer: 'California',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600dd41b71128e7eb0127823',
		selection: ['Judicial', 'Executive', 'Legislative', 'No branch'],
		question: 'Which branch of US government evaluates laws',
		answer: 'Judicial',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	},
	{
		_id: '600dd46971128e7eb0127824',
		selection: ['4', '6', '2', '12'],
		question: 'Acid rain has an average ph of',
		answer: '4',
		__v: { $numberInt: '0' }
	}
]
